Oliver Tambo Papers 2000.0144
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series B: Office of the President, 1962-1992
  - ANC - Miscellaneous Topics (Box B10)
    - Negotiations (Box B10., Folder 8)
      - Memoranda/Reports (10 items) (Box B10., Folder 8.1)
        Items include Responses to ANC Discussion Paper on the issue of Negotiations from UK Region'; Notes on the meeting between Mr Hendrik van der Merwe and the Chief Representative (and M. Netsianda) on 30 August 1989; Notes of the Meeting between the Chief Representative (and M Netsianda) and Mildred Nevile, Coordinator, Southern Africa Coalition on 11 August 1989; Notes on meeting between Mr. Patrick Fairweather, Under-Secretary of State ( Africa) in Foreign and Commonwealth Office (and Tim Dowse) and the Chief Representative, Comrade Mendi Msimang, (and M. Netsianda) on 31 August 1989; Notes on the meeting on 15 August 1989 between Foreign and Commonwealth Office ( Tim Dowse and Jeffrey Berg) and the African National Congress Chief Representative and Mamatho Netsianda); Notes on meeting between Jimmy Kolker (First Secretary US Embassy London) and Bill Lucas (First Secretary US Embassy Pretoria) and the Chief Representative (and M. Netsianda) on 30 August 1989; Notes on the Meeting between Mr. Andrew Pearce and the Chief Representative, comrade Mendi Msimang (and M. Netsianda) on 30 August 1989.
      - Miscellaneous Reports/Papers (4 items) (Box B10., Folder 8.2)
        Items include Dr. Sibusiso Bengu’s response to the ANC Discussion Paper on the Issue of Negotiations.
      - Press Statement/Extracts from the Submission of the ANC to the Meeting between the ANC and the Government, Tuynhuis, 1990 October 8 (Box B10., Folder 8.3)
    - Pretoria Minute (Box B10., Folder 9)
      - General (Box B10., Folder 9.1)
        - Report (Box B10., Folder 9.1.1)
          - Update on the Transition Process: Paper III - The Pretoria Minute and Working Group Report ( Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights under Law), 1990 August 6
      - Working Group re suspension of armed action (Box B10., Folder 9.2)
        - Briefing Notes on the Working Group Agreement entered into between the ANC and the Government, 1991 February 12 (Box B10., Folder 9.2.1)
        - Press Release (Box B10., Folder 9.2.2)
      - Working Group re release of ANC Prisoners, etc. (Box B10., Folder 9.3)
        - Correspondence/Reports/Press Statements (7 items)
          Items include Reports of the Working Group under Paragraph 2 and 3 of the Pretoria Minute; Political Imprisonment in South Africa: Joint Publication of the Human Rights Commission and IDAF.
    - Public Administrators (Box B10., Folder 10)
      - Correspondence/Memoranda/Reports (7 items), 1988-1990
        Items include Correspondence re Body of Profession Public Administrators (within the ANC); Provisional Body of Public Administrators: Planning Seminar, 1988; Report re ANC/ SIDA Seminar on Administrative Development Programme, 8 - 19 May 1989; ANC Administrative Study, May 1989.
    - Refugees (South African) (Box B10., Folder 11)
      - Memorandum Re SACC visit to Mazimbu, Dakawa and Refugee Camps in Botswana and Tanzania, 1989 October 6
      - Miscellaneous
        - Protocol between ANC and the Office of the United Nations High commissioner for refugees ( UNCHR) relating to the repatriation of South African Refugees (Master Copy?)
        - Pamphlet-- South African Refugees - Tanzania
    - Smear Campaigns (9 items) (Box B10., Folder 12)
    - Strategy and Tactics (Box B10., Folder 13)
      - Reports/Papers (6 items) (Box B10., Folder 13.1)
        Items include Suggested Tactics and Strategy in the Mobilisation and Organisation of Africans for the Revolution; Reflections on the political strategy of the South African Revolution.
      - Publications (2 items) (Box B10., Folder 13.2)
        - Forward to Freedom - strategy, tactics and programme of the ANC: Published by the ANC, Morogoro, Tanzania
        - Advance to National Democracy - Guidelines on Strategy and Tactics of the ANC, 1991 February
- Series C: Special Topics
  - Conferences (Box C1)
    - Conference of Independent African States, Addis Ababa, 1960 June (Box C1., Folder 1)
      - Invitation--Addressed to Oliver Tambo (Box C1., Folder 1.1)
      - Summary Records of 1 - 6 Plenary Meetings (Box C1., Folder 1.1.2)
      - Speeches/Statements (7 items) (Box C1., Folder 1.3)
        Items include Speech by Mr Ako Adjei, Minister of Foreign Affairs of Ghana; Speech by H. E. Dr. Whabi El Buri, Head of the Libya n Delegation; Closing Address of J. Rudolph Grimes, Secretary of State of the Liberia n Delegation.
      - Resolutions of committee I - III (Box C1., Folder 1.4)
      - Miscellaneous (1 items) (Box C1., Folder 1.5)
        News Bulletin.
    - The Third Afro-Asian People’s Solidarity Conference, Moshi, Taganyika, 1963 February 4 - 11 (Box C1., Folder 2)
      - Speeches (2 items) (Box C1., Folder 2.1)
        Julius Nyere; Jomo Kenyatta.
      - Speeches of Heads of Delegations (22 items)
        Doc. No. 109/III - 162/III } Documents Missing (Includes Speech by Oliver Tambo: Doc. No. 151/III).
      - Declarations/Resolutions (Box C1., Folder 2.2)
      - Miscellaneous Reports (Box C1., Folder 2.3)
        Items include notes taken by Oliver Tambo; Some suggestions (sic) on the initiation in Japan of a movement for the boycott of South Africa n goods; Report on proceedings.
      - Miscellaneous (Box C1., Folder 2.4)
        Budget/Mailing List for Conference.
    - Organisation for Afro-Asian People's Solidarity (Box C1., Folder 3)
      - Resolutions and Recommendations of the 6th Session of the Executive Committee, Nicosia, 1963 September 10 - 12
    - International Seminar on Apartheid and Colonialism in Southern Africa, Kitwe, Zambia, 1967 July 24 - August 4 (Box C1., Folder 4)
      - Paper (Box C1., Folder 4.1)
        Paper presented by the ANC. 14p. Ts.
    - World Council of Churches: Consultation on Racism, London, 1969 May (Box C1., Folder 5)
      - Correspondence (Box C1., Folder 5.1)
        Correspondence addressed to Oliver Tambo.
      - List of participants (Box C1., Folder 5.2)
      - Papers (10 items) (Box C1., Folder 5.3)
        Items include Racism a lighted power-keg (sic) of violence in Southern Africa; The Asians in East Africa; Black Ecumenical Power; Minorities of Asia; Racism and its theological significance for the Church; European thinking on race.
      - Reports (Box C1., Folder 5.4)
        - Working Group I "Spiritual and Moral Issues in Opposing Racism"
        - Working Group II "The Realities of Racism Today"
        - Plan for an Ecumenical Programme to Combat Racism
      - Miscellaneous (Box C1., Folder 5.5)
        Hand drawn map of Southern Africa.
    - International Conference for support of victims of Colonialism and Apartheid in South Africa, Oslo, Norway, 1973 April (Box C1., Folder 6)
      - Provisional List of Participants/List of Documents (Box C1., Folder 6.1)
      - Papers/Proposals (4 items) (Box C1., Folder 6.2)
        Items include Education and Training Programmes, Background paper - Lars-Funnar Eriksson.
    - Fourth Conference of Non Aligned Countries, Algiers, 1973 September 5 - 8 (Box C1., Folder 7)
      - Agenda (French) (Box C1., Folder 7.1)
      - Inaugural Address, Delivered by President Houari Boumediene of the Revolutionary Council and President of the Council of Ministers (Box C1., Folder 7.2)
      - Proposals/Declarations/Working Papers/Studies (45 items) (Box C1., Folder 7.3)
        Includes Draft Resolution on Apartheid and Racial Discrimination in South Africa, Submitted by the ANC.
      - Conference Bulletin (Box C1., Folder 7.4)
      - Miscellaneous (2 items) (Box C1., Folder 7.5)
      - Conference of Foreign Ministers - Report (Box C1., Folder 7.6)
    - Fourth Conference of Non Aligned Countries: Meeting of the Bureau, Algiers, 1974 March 19 - 21 (Box C1., Folder 8)
      - Final Document (Box C1., Folder 8.1)
    - Pan-African Youth Movement Conference, Benghazi, Libya, 1974 March (Box C1., Folder 9)
      - Papers (4 items) (Box C1., Folder 9.1)
        Items include speech delivered by the Head of the ZAPU Youth Front, Comrade Stephen Vuma; Contribution of the SWAPO Youth League.
    - Sixth Pan-African Congress, Dar Es Salaam, 1974 June (Box C1., Folder 10)
      - Correspondence (4 items) (Box C1., Folder 10.1)
        Items include Invitation to attend Congress; request for Oliver Tambo to prepare a paper for the conference.
      - Briefing Paper/Secretariat Report/Registration Form/Reservation Form for Accommodation
      - Speeches/Messages (Box C1., Folder 10.3)
        - President Nyere’s Speech to the Pan African Congress
        - Message by President Ahm Ed Sekou Toure
        - Speech by the Head of the Cuba n delegation
      - Report--Document of Cuba n Delegation (Box C1., Folder 10.4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box C1., Folder 10.5)
    - International NGO Conference against Apartheid and Colonialism in Africa, Palais des Nations, Geneva, 1974 September 2 - 5 (Box C1., Folder 11)
      - Correspondence/Invitations (2 items) (Box C1., Folder 11.1)
      - Reports/Draft Resolution (4 items) (Box C1., Folder 11.2)
      - Papers (11 items) (Box C1., Folder 11.3)
        Items include Introductory Paper submitted by the ANC (with accompanying draft); "Apartheid must be outlawed," Professor I. Blishtchenko (Institute of International Relations, Moscow); "Apartheid and the Law," submitted by the ANC; "Legal Aspects of the Armed Struggle of the Liberation Movements," Georges Abi-Saab; "The Republic of South Africa," A. P. O’Dowd, Anti-Apartheid Movement; " Rhodesia: Recent Political Developments," M. D. Terry, Anti-Apartheid Movement; " Namibia: Political Developments during 1973/74," Roger Murray, Friends of Namibia Committee; "Political Trials and Detentions in Namibia," SWAPO.
      - Statements/Messages (4 items) (Box C1., Folder 11.4)
        Items include "Statement of the African Liberation Movements," Presented by Alfred Nzo, Secretary General of the ANC.
    - General Telexes re Conferences, 1975 (Box C1., Folder 12)
    - Conference of Developing Countries on Raw Material, Dakar, 1975 August 3 - 8 (Box C1., Folder 13)
      - Statement-- B. M. Saliwa ( ANC) (Box C1., Folder 13.1)
    - Conference of Ministers for Foreign Affairs of Non-Aligned Countries, Lima, 1975 August 25 - 29 (Box C1., Folder 14)
      - Reports/Miscellaneous Items (12 items) (Box C1., Folder 14.1)
      - Statements/Messages (13 items) (Box C1., Folder 14.2)
    - World Conference against Apartheid, Racism and Colonialism in Southern Africa, Lisbon, 1977 June 16 - 19 (Box C1., Folder 15)
      - Paper (Box C1., Folder 15.1)
        - "South Africa’s Military Build-up," Presented by the British Anti-Apartheid Movement
        - Contribution (Paper/Statement) of the Women’s International Democratic Federation (Delivered by Fanny Edelman (General Secretary)
      - Resolution/Message (Box C1., Folder 15.2)
        - Economic Commission - Resolution
        - Message to the People of South Africa
      - Information Bulletin (Box C1., Folder 15.3)
    - World Conference for Action against Apartheid, Lagos, 1977 August (Box C1., Folder 16)
      - Composition of the Steering Committee (Box C1., Folder 16.1)
      - Guidelines for the Conference (Box C1., Folder 16.2)
      - Declaration (Box C1., Folder 16.3)
        Includes Amendments to Draft Declaration; General Declaration; Declaration du Secretaire General.
      - Speeches (Box C1., Folder 16.4)
        - Speech by Olaf Palme, Sweden
        - Speech given by Mr. Odvar Nordli, Prime Minister of Norway
      - Papers (Box C1., Folder 16.5)
        - Paper No.2, "Unite in Action for the Liberation of Southern Africa - a plea to all nations" (Rev. Canon L. J. Collins/President - IDAF)
        - Paper No.4, "Apartheid South Africa - The Illegitimate Regime" ( Kadar Asmal)
      - Statements/Messages (5 items) (See also: Press Releases)
        Includes ANC Statement.
      - Press Releases (7 items) (Box C1., Folder 16.7)
        Items include: Statements by 23 States heard in debate (See also Statements/Messages).
    - World Conference to Combat Racism and Racial Discrimination, Geneva, 1978 August 14 - 25 (Box C1., Folder 17)
      - Statement--"Statement by National Liberation Movements on the necessity of eliminating all and every form of racism, apartheid and racial discrimination," presented by ANC and the patriotic front. (Box C1., Folder 17.1)
      - Report/Speech by Mark Shope on the Conference (Box C1., Folder 17.2)
    - International Non Governmental Organisation Conference, Geneva, 1978 August 28 - 31 (Box C1., Folder 18)
      - Reports (Box C1., Folder 18.1)
        - Mark Shope--Meetings with delegates from other organisations
        - Lars Gunnar Erikson on the Problem of our students in Nigeria
        - Meetings with Lars Gunnar Erikson/ Mark Shope, 1978 August 31
    - Fourth Bi-Annual Conference of the African Association of Political Science, Maputo, 1979 (Box C1., Folder 19)
      - Introductory document (Box C1., Folder 19.1)
        Includes Announcement; Theme of the Conference; Organisation; Panels and Convenors, etc.
    - Southern Africa: The Time to Choose, 1982 March 11 - 13 (Box C1., Folder 20)
      - List of Principal Documents/Report (Box C1., Folder 20.1)
      - Speeches/Message ( 4 items) (Box C1., Folder 20.2)
      - Conference Papers (Box C1., Folder 20.3)
        - 1 - "Recent developments in South Africa"
        - 3 - " South Africa’s Military and Nuclear Build-up"
        - 4 - " South Africa’s War against Independent Africa"
        - 5 - "Southern Africa - British, European and Western Policy"
    - Fourth Annual Meeting of the Southern African Labour Commission, Gabarone, Botswana, 1982 August 30 (Box C1., Folder 21)
      - List of participants (Box C1., Folder 21.1)
      - Speeches/Statements (5 items) (Box C1., Folder 21.2)
    - Emergency International Conference in Solidarity with the People of South Africa, Addis Ababa, 1985 October 11 - 13 (Box C1., Folder 22)
      - Provisional list of participants (Box C1., Folder 22.1)
      - Address/Motion of thanks (Box C1., Folder 22.2)
    - Notes on Discussions held by President Dr. K. E. Kaunda, with a delegation of South African Businessmen at State House, 21p. Ts., 1985 July 11 (Box C1., Folder 23)
    - World Conference on Sanctions against racist South Africa, UNESCO House, Paris, 1986 June 16 - 20 (Box C1., Folder 24)
      - Declaration--First Working Draft for the Declaration of the World Conference on Sanctions against racist South Africa, 23p. Ts. (Box C1., Folder 24.1)
    - 8th Non-Aligned Conference, Harare, 1986 August/September (Box C1., Folder 25)
      - Provisional list of participants/Addendum (Box C1., Folder 25.1)
      - Speeches/Statements (Box C1., Folder 25.2)
        - Countries A - I (13 items) (Box C1., Folder 25.2.1)
        - Countries P - Z (16 items) (Box C1., Folder 25.2.2)
        - Statement prepared by the ANC, Department of Information and Publicity (Box C1., Folder 25.2.3)
      - Reports (4 items) (Box C1., Folder 25.3)
      - Draft Political Declaration (Box C1., Folder 25.4)
      - Miscellaneous (3 items) (Box C1., Folder 25.5)
        Items include Press Releases; Pamphlet South Africa imposes sanctions against its neighbours.
    - Documents of the Conference of Ministers for Foreign Affairs of Non-Aligned Countries, Luanda, 1986 September 2 - 7 (Box C1., Folder 26)
    - Dakar Declaration ( IDASA), A Joint Communiqué, 1987 July 11 (Box C1., Folder 27)
      - Report (Box C1., Folder 27.1)
    - 8th Non-Aligned Conference on Children, Repression and the Law in Apartheid South Africa, Harare, 1987 September 24 - 27 (Box C1., Folder 28)
      - Correspondence/Memorandum/Background Documents, ( DPSC, Kader Asmal, N. Haysom)/working Papers/Statement/Declarations (5 items) (Box C1., Folder 28.1)
    - 17th African-American Conference, Gabarone, Botswana, 1987 January 12 - 16 (Box C1., Folder 29)
      - Report (Box C1., Folder 29.1)
    - 6th PTA Summit, 1987 December 3 - 4 (Box C1., Folder 30)
      - Invitation Extended to Oliver Tambo by the President of Uganda, Yoweri Kaguta Museveni (Includes reply by Oliver Tambo) (Box C1., Folder 30.1)
      - Programme/Agenda (Box C1., Folder 30.2)
    - Harare Symposium on the Survival and Development of Children in the Frontline States and Southern Africa, 1988 March 1 - 5 (Box C1., Folder 31)
      - Correspondence (3 items) (Box C1., Folder 31.1)
        Sally Mugabe; Oliver Tambo.
      - Draft Agenda/List, Members of the Bureau of the Symposium (Box C1., Folder 31.2)
      - Background Paper--Artists and Intellectuals Symposium for Child Survival and Development in the Frontline States and in Southern Africa, Harare, January 1988, includes a table of contents, 33p. Ts. (Box C1., Folder 31.3)
    - 19th African-American Conference, Lusaka, Zambia, 1989 January 9 - 13 (Box C1., Folder 32)
      - Conference Package--Participant Oliver Tambo (Box C1., Folder 32.1)
        Includes Agenda; List of Participants; Workshops; Departure Form.
    - Meeting between Frontline States and OAU, Harare, 1989 March 21 (Box C1., Folder 33)
      - Telex--Invitation extended to Oliver Tambo to attend meeting (Box C1., Folder 33.1)
        - Miscellaneous--Notes for the Frontline States Meeting
      - Agenda (Drafts)/Programme (Box C1., Folder 33.2)
      - Statement-- Kenneth Kaunda (Box C1., Folder 33.3)
      - Memoranda/Reports/Statements, etc. (5 items) (Box C1., Folder 33.4)
    - Five Freedoms Forum/ ANC, "The Role of Whites in a Changing Society,", 1989 June 29 - July 2 (Box C1., Folder 34)
      Items include Programme; Lists of delegates; Reports/Papers; Conference Package; Welcoming Address - O. R. Tambo; Press Statement - O. R. Tambo.
    - Free the Children from Apartheid - summary report from a working conference for Swedish national and local NGO’s, Stockholm, with guests from Angola, Mozambique, Namibia, South Africa and Zimbabwe, 1989 September 22 - 23 (Box C1., Folder 35)
    - Conference of Joint Executives of the ANC and PAC, Harare, 1991 April 15 - 16 (Box C1., Folder 36)
      - Resolutions/Joint Communiqué (4 items) (Box C1., Folder 36.1)
    - Miscellaneous (20 items) (Box C1., Folder 37)
      Items include Social Scientists' Preparatory Committee - preparation of papers; Notes on the Migrant Labour Conference, (1978 April 1); Conference of African Governmental Experts on Technical Cooperation among African Countries on Human Resources, Development and Utilisation, Libreville ( Gabon), (1982 August 2 - 11); Final Communiqué of the Second Extra-Ordinary Meeting of the Authority of the Preferential Trade Area for Eastern and Southern African States, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia (1988 May 24); Joint Communiqué of the Socialist International, The Socialist Group of the European Parliament, the Frontline States Parties and the Liberation Movements - Harare Conference on Southern Africa (1989 February 15 - 16).
    - Frontline States Summit Meetings (Box C1., Folder 37.1)
  - Countries (Box C2)
    Includes Heads of State; Embassies; Governmental Bodies/Burroughs/Cities; Parliamentary Opposition Groupings/Extra-Parliamentary Opposition Groupings e.g. PLO.
    - Algeria (Box C2., Folder 1)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (6 items), 1971, 1977, 1989-1990 (Box C2., Folder 1.1)
        Correspondents include Chadli Bendjedid. Subjects include 15th Anniversary of Algerian Independence; Nelson Mandela.
      - General (3 items) (Box C2., Folder 1.2)
        Includes News for Algeria (Embassy of the Democratic People’s Republica of Algeria).
    - Angola (Box C2., Folder 2)
      - Correspondence Oliver Tambo (1 item), 1988 (Box C2., Folder 2.1)
        Correspondence with: Jose Eduardo dos Santos. Subject "13th Independence Anniversary of the People’s Republic of Angola."
      - General (Box C2., Folder 2.2)
        - Report of the International Mission of Inquiry into the acts of aggression perpetrated by South Africa against the P. R. of Angola, 1980 August 6 - 13
        - Meeting with MPLA (Handwritten notes)
      - Speeches/Messages (10 items) (Box C2., Folder 2.3)
        - Dr. Agostinho Neto's speech at the "Cidadela" Meeting, 1975 February 4
        - Speech delivered by Agostinho Neto, President of the MPLA and of The People’s Republic of Angola, at the Opening Session of the 29 Meeting of the OAU Coordinating Committee for the Liberation of Africa, Luanda, 1977 June 14
        - Message of the ANC to the 1st Congress of the MPLA, Luanda, 1977 December
      - MPLA Pamphlets (3 items + 1 duplicate) (Box C2., Folder 2.4)
    - Argentina (Box C2., Folder 3)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (1 items), 1986 (Box C2., Folder 3.1)
        Correspondent--Argentine Committee for the Independence of Namibia and Eradication of Apartheid; Carlos H. Bianchi (Diplomat). Subject--invitation to participate in the First All American Congress on Southern Africa; breaking of diplomatic relations with South Africa.
    - Australia (Box C2., Folder 4)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (5 items), 1989 (Box C2., Folder 4.1)
        Correspondents include Gareth Evans; Robin Nestdale (See also: UNICEF); Dr. Helen Ware.
      - General (Box C2., Folder 4.2)
        - Correspondence (2 items)
          Subjects--1973 Springbok tour; Campaign against Racial Exploitation (CARE) Conference on Namibia, 1988.
        - Programme/Media Kit: Visit to Australia of Oliver Tambo, 1987 March 27 - April 12
        - Speech Delivered by Justice Einfeld, the then President of the Human Rights and Equal Opportunity Commission, on the occasion of Oliver Tambo's visit to Australia
    - Barbados (1 item), 1988 (Box C2., Folder 5)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence
    - Botswana (Box C2., Folder 6)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (10 items), undated, 1988-1991 (Box C2., Folder 6.1)
        Correspondents include Dr. Kenneth Koma ( Botswana National Front); Q. K. J. Masire. Subjects include Botswana citizens (and one South Africa n refugee) killed in a South African Defence Force raid; 70th Birthday of Nelson Mandela; message of condolence on the death of Johnny Makatini and Bheki Mlangeni.
      - General (Box C2., Folder 6.2)
        - Correspondence (3 items) (Box C2., Folder 6.2.1)
        - Report/Minutes (Box C2., Folder 6.2.2)
          - Report on Botswana - Act to Control Political Refugees, 1968 November 5
          - Minutes - Meeting between ANC delegation and delegation of the Botswana government, 1987 September 17
        - Speeches/Messages (5 items) (Box C2., Folder 6.2.3)
          Items include Speeches by Seretse Khama, 1969-1971.
    - Brazil (Box C2., Folder 7)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (1 item), 1991 (Box C2., Folder 7.1)
        Correspondent-- Brazil ian Committee of Solidarity with the Peoples of South Africa and Namibia-COMAFRICA). Subject--Freedom of the City of Rio de Janeiro granted to Oliver Tambo.
    - Bulgaria (Box C2., Folder 8)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (10 items), 1979, 1987, 1989 (Box C2., Folder 8.1)
        Correspondents include Bulgaria n Committee for Solidarity with the Peoples of Asia and Africa; Dr. D. Romanov (Ambassador). Subjects include granting of scholarships for Higher Education; message of condolence received on the death of Johnny Makatini; Namibia.
    - Cambodia (Box C2., Folder 9)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (1 item), 1990
        Correspondent Heng Samrin.
    - Canada (Box C2., Folder 10)
      - Oliver Tambo Correspondence (3 items), 1989-1990 (Box C2., Folder 10.1)